<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Klarissa&#39;s Website</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Klarissa&#39;s Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Falling in love with Python...</title>
      <link>/post/2020/12/10/backup-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/12/10/backup-post/</guid>
      <description>Falling in love with Python... Python can do some really cool things. R is great, don&#39;t get me wrong, but there is just something about python that actually makes running codes seem simple. For example, one of the easiest things you can do in python is to use it as a calculator. Running simple math equations on python is as simple as typing it out because python does all the math for you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can you Predict Whether you will get Accepted into Medical School?</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>Klarissa Flores (kmf2747) The dataset &#39;MedGPA&#39; gives information regarding 55 medical school applicants. The variables include whether they were accepted or denied, the sex of the applicant, their BCPM GPA (which is their grade point average in the subjects of biology, chemistry, physics, and math), their overall college GPA, their subscores in areas of verbal reasoning, physical science, writing, and biological sciences (I didn&#39;t care much about these subscore variables), their MCAT score, and the number of applications they sent out to medical schools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What You Can Tell About a State from Their Level of Education</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>Klarissa Flores (kmf2747) library(dplyr) library(tidyverse)  Data The dataset crime contains information about how hate crimes may be tied to income inequality in the US. It is part of the fivethirtyeight package on R. It includes data about median household income, the average number of hate crimes recorded by the FBI and the Southern Poverty Law Center, the share of the population that voted for Trump, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description> Check out some of my coding projects below:
 Wrangling &amp;amp; Exploratory Data Analysis
 Modeling, Inference, Prediction
  -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
